I was standing there
and I was like
how did you do
that And the
replied I'm not kidding
you the mad lad
figured it out on
its own And then
it walked me through
every single step How
it got a from
me but there was
no file ending So
it the file It
found that it was
audio but a format
so it it And
then it was looking
for something to the
but I didn't have
it But then it
found an OpenAI key
It sent the whole
thing to the It
got it back and
then it All of
that in nine seconds
Can you imagine I
didn't build any of
that For me this
was the moment where
I thought
this is something new
This is not a
chatbot give up
Agents improvise
And you know I
was sold